<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Philly Community Wireless</title>
    <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Philly Community Wireless</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://phillycommunitywireless.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PCW Outreach Coordinator</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/outreachjob/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/outreachjob/</guid>
      <description>Philly Community Wireless Job Posting Who we are: Philly Community Wireless is a volunteer-led coalition of technologists and organizers working to build community controlled wireless internet networks in Philadelphia. We are committed to growing tech literacy, expanding internet access, and building community autonomy with our neighbors. We believe that internet access is a human right. We work to build out the physical infrastructure along with community engagement with the network. Our goal is to make a robust wifi network managed by the people that use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/people/</guid>
      <description>= organizer = technologist = teacher = researcher
Administrative Team Executive Director
Alex Wermer-Colan \
Systems Administrator
Allan Gomez Technician
Mir Detre Community Engagement Liaison
Chris Mehretab Install Lead
Dylan Huthcinson Board of Directors Will Dean Research and Data Services Librarian, Temple University Libraries
Jonathan Latko Computer Recycling Center, Temple University
Jessa Lingel Associate Professor, Annenberg School for Communication, University of Pennsylvania
Rev. Michael A. Major Board President, Called to Serve CDC</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Our team includes volunteers and staff from a wide array of local and national organizations. For more information, visit our people page.
The Big Picture Alliance recently completed a documentary film about the early stages of the PCW project. Check it out on YouTube
For up to date info on the project, sign up for our newsletter!
Vision Just before the COVID-19 pandemic hit, a detailed study published by the Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia found that a mere 53% of Black residents and 44% of Latinx residents in Philadelphia have broadband connections (Alvaro 2020).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/airmonitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/airmonitor/</guid>
      <description>Act on Air: The Philly Air Monitor Project Philly Community Wireless is partnering with other organizations around the city, including the Clean Air Council and Temple University&amp;rsquo;s Geography and Urban Studies Program, to deploy Purple Air Monitors on our network.
Measuring Air Quality Purple Air monitors allow residents to asses:
If their air quality is good in their area How it compares to other parts of the city. Purple Air Monitors Purple air monitors enable communities to engage in citizen science around pollution in their neighborhoods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Coverage Map</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/networkmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/networkmap/</guid>
      <description>Philly Community Wireless Wifi Coverage Map To view the map in fullscreen, visit this webpage.
This map focuses on showing the overall network architecture. Points on the map represent outdoor wifi access points primarily. Any area covered by the heatmap should have PCW signal available for a free wifi connection.
Please keep in mind that the heatmap is not accurate at the street-level, and if you cannot access the wifi network in any given space in the city, you may need to walk around a street corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/faq/</guid>
      <description>Who are we? What is Philly Community Wireless? Philly Community Wireless is a project to develop community-owned mesh networks in North Philly. We are a working group of organizers, technologists, academics, public school teachers, and City Hall staffers in Philadelphia. During a time of social distancing and online teaching, roughly half of the city’s public school students lack a wifi connection at home. In certain neighborhoods, even more residents lack any connection to the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/termsofservice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/termsofservice/</guid>
      <description>Philly Community Wireless is a free, public wifi network. To use this free wifi network, you agree to our following Terms of Service.
Terms of Service The Philly Community Wireless Project, a fiscally sponsored project of the Movement Alliance Project (“PCWP”) and its backhaul provider, PhillyWisper (“PW”), support net neutrality and a free and open Internet without throttling, zero-rating, or tracking people’s usage for money, advertising, or other forms of consideration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCW Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Values of Participation This is a safe space. We encourage discussion of sensitive and difficult topics so that we can support each other and problem solve together. At the same time, we strive to uphold spaces where people with a plurality of voices and experiences can participate in full. Due to the sensitive or private nature of some elements of the project, please be cognizant to avoid sharing identifying information, and remember that anything you do share is seen by other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Notice</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Effective Date: March 1, 2021
Last Updated: May 21, 2021
We at Philadelphia Community Wireless Project, a fiscally sponsored project of the Movement Alliance Project (&amp;quot;PCWP&amp;quot;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;) are strongly committed to transparency, and we want you (&amp;quot;you&amp;quot; or &amp;ldquo;your&amp;rdquo;) to understand how we collect, use, share and protect your personal information, as well as how you can manage the personal information we collect. This Privacy Notice applies to your interactions with us, including attending our events or participating in our programs, or your use of our website (www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/resources/</guid>
      <description>Effective Date: March 1, 2021
Last Updated: January 4, 2024
Below are some more materials and resources to help you find digital resources for wifi access, computer use, and more. Check them out!
Free Desktop Computers and Digital Literacy Training Organization: Digital Equity Center at Temple University
Location: 1918 N 11th St, Philadelphia PA 19122 Description: Non-profit and community requests for refurbished and new computer equipment. Residents of Philadelphia are eligible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>We love volunteers! We&amp;rsquo;re a volunteer-led coalition working to build community controlled wireless internet networks in Philadelphia. Below we&amp;rsquo;ve outlined ways that volunteers can contribute.
If you’re interested in getting involved, please fill out our Volunteer Sign-Up Form.
Tech Volunteers The Tech Team is actively seeking volunteers to help with our installation process: attending in-person trainings and work days in Norris Square, configuring our networking hardware, and installing equipment in homes and on rooftops.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
