<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Philly Community Wireless</title>
    <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Philly Community Wireless</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://phillycommunitywireless.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project Manager Job Posting</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/job/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/job/</guid>
      <description>Philly Community Wireless (PCW) is a collective impact initiative consisting of allied community organizations based in the neighborhoods of Fairhill and Kensington. We are building community-owned and -operated internet infrastructures in order to democratize access, promote digital literacy, and fight digital inequity with free, net-neutral broadband service in North Philadelphia.
Through funding from the Independence Public Media Foundation and the Digital Literacy Alliance at the Mayor’s Fund for Philadelphia, PCW seeks a full-time Project Manager to lead this volunteer-driven initiative over the next two years as we partner with nonprofits, local businesses, and immigrant/LEP communities in the Norris Square Park neighborhood to develop an alternative model of community-based network stewardship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Our team includes volunteers and staff from a wide array of local and national organizations. For more information, visit our people page.
Vision Just before the COVID-19 pandemic hit, a detailed study published by the Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia found that a mere 53% of Black residents and 44% of Latinx residents in Philadelphia have broadband connections (Alvaro 2020). The pandemic has dramatically demonstrated the implications of this digital divide and exacerbated existing inequalities for students, business owners, job seekers, and many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/faq/</guid>
      <description>What is Philly Community Wireless? Philly Community Wireless is a project to develop community-owned mesh networks in North Philly. We are a working group of organizers, technologists, academics, public school teachers, and City Hall staffers in Philadelphia. During a time of social distancing and online teaching, roughly half of the city’s public school students lack a wifi connection at home. In certain neighborhoods, even more residents lack any connection to the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get connected</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/getconnected/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/getconnected/</guid>
      <description>Sign Up! If you live in the Norris Square Park neighborhood of North Philadelphia and want to get connected to free wireless internet, or host an antenna to connect your neighbors, please fill out our Sign Up Form!
The Installation Process Philly Community Wireless works with PhillyWisper, a wireless internet service provider, who installs rooftop antennas that we use to provide a free wifi network to the neighborhood residents and public spaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/people/</guid>
      <description>= organizer  = technologist  = teacher  = researcher
Organizational leads Admin Lead
Alex Wermer-Colan   Digital Scholarship Coordinator, Temple University, Scholars Studio
Tech Lead
Addie Barron  Technologist and Software Engineer
Outreach Leads
Heather Lewis-Weber   Sr. Coordinator of Community Engagement, Temple University, College of Liberal Arts
Kate Goodman  Community Initiatives Specialist, Free Library of Philadelphia
Staff Community Engagement Liaison
Chris Mehretab</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCW Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Values of Participation This is a safe space. We encourage discussion of sensitive and difficult topics so that we can support each other and problem solve together. At the same time, we strive to uphold spaces where people with a plurality of voices and experiences can participate in full. Due to the sensitive or private nature of some elements of the project, please be cognizant to avoid sharing identifying information, and remember that anything you do share is seen by other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Notice</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Effective Date: March 1, 2021
Last Updated: May 21, 2021
 We at Philadelphia Community Wireless Project, a fiscally sponsored project of the Movement Alliance Project (&amp;quot;PCWP&amp;quot;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;we&amp;quot;) are strongly committed to transparency, and we want you (&amp;quot;you&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;your&amp;quot;) to understand how we collect, use, share and protect your personal information, as well as how you can manage the personal information we collect. This Privacy Notice applies to your interactions with us, including attending our events or participating in our programs, or your use of our website (www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/resources/</guid>
      <description>Below are some more materials and resources to help you find digital resources for wifi access, computer use, and more. Check them out!
Free Desktop Computers and Digital Literacy Training Organization: Digital Equity Center at Temple University
Location: 1918 N 11th St, Philadelphia PA 19122
Description: Non-profit and community requests for refurbished and new computer equipment. Residents of Philadelphia are eligible. Register: Visit this link https://techforphilly.com or call
Free Tablets Organization: TechOWL Connect with Tech Description: Connect with Tech gives free tablets and tech support to people who have trouble getting technology and health care services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>Our network is being built by and for our communities. To get involved, just reach out to one of our team leads based on your area(s) of interest. We are currently looking for volunteers with availability to work on-site and contribute to the installation of hardware.
Tech The tech team is primarily looking for volunteers who can donate time and effort to our installation process: attending in-person trainings and workdays in Norris Square, configuring our networking hardware, and installing equipment in homes and on rooftops.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
