<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Philly Community Wireless</title>
    <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Philly Community Wireless</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://phillycommunitywireless.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Our team includes volunteers and staff from a wide array of local and national organizations. For more information, visit our people page.
Vision Just before the COVID-19 pandemic hit, a detailed study published by the Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia found that a mere 53% of Black residents and 44% of Latinx residents in Philadelphia have broadband connections (Alvaro 2020). The pandemic has dramatically demonstrated the implications of this digital divide and exacerbated existing inequalities for students, business owners, job seekers, and many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/faq/</guid>
      <description>What is Philly Community Wireless? Philly Community Wireless is a project to develop community-owned mesh networks in North Philly. We are a working group of organizers, technologists, academics, public school teachers, and City Hall staffers in Philadelphia. During a time of social distancing and online teaching, roughly half of the city’s public school students lack a wifi connection at home. In certain neighborhoods, even more residents lack any connection to the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get connected</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/getconnected/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/getconnected/</guid>
      <description>If you live in the Norris Square Park neighborhood of North Philadelphia and would like to sign up to host a rooftop antenna or a mesh kit in your home, please fill out our Sign Up Form!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/people/</guid>
      <description>= organizer
 = technologist
 = teacher
 = researcher
Organizational leads Admin Lead
Alex Wermer-Colan  
Digital Scholarship Coordinator, Temple University, Scholars Studio
Tech Lead
Addie Barron 
Independent Technologist
Outreach Leads
Heather Lewis-Weber  
Sr. Coordinator of Community Engagement, Temple University, College of Liberal Arts
Kate Goodman 
Community Initiatives Specialist, Free Library of Philadelphia
Staff Community Engagement Liaison
Chris Mehretab 
PCW Steering Committee Will Dean</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>Our network is being built by and for our communities. To get involved, just reach out to one of our team leads based on your area(s) of interest.
Tech The tech team is primarily looking for volunteers who can donate time and effort to our installation process: attending in-person trainings and workdays in Norris Square, configuring our networking hardware, and installing equipment in homes and on rooftops. We are all in the process of learning these skills, so you&amp;rsquo;ll be trained in a collaborative environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact us   phillycommunitywireless@gmail.com
  215-316-5761
  Find us on Facebook</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Notice</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Effective Date: March 1, 2021
Last Updated: May 21, 2021
 We at Philadelphia Community Wireless Project, a fiscally sponsored project of the Movement Alliance Project (&amp;quot;PCWP&amp;quot;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;we&amp;quot;) are strongly committed to transparency, and we want you (&amp;quot;you&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;your&amp;quot;) to understand how we collect, use, share and protect your personal information, as well as how you can manage the personal information we collect. This Privacy Notice applies to your interactions with us, including attending our events or participating in our programs, or your use of our website (www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
