<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Philly Community Wireless</title>
    <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Philly Community Wireless</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://phillycommunitywireless.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/people/</guid>
      <description>= organizer = technologist = teacher = researcher
Administrative Team Executive Director
Alex Wermer-Colan alex@phillycommunitywireless.org
Systems Administrator
Allan Gomez allan@phillycommunitywireless.org
Technician
Mir Detre mir@phillycommunitywireless.org
Community Engagement Liaison
Chris Mehretab chris@phillycommunitywireless.org
Install Lead Dylan Hutchinson dylan@phillycommunitywireless.org
Install Lead
Eugene Ryoo Outreach Coordinator Leanne Przybylowski leanne@phillycommunitywireless.org
Board of Directors Will Dean Research and Data Services Librarian, Temple University Libraries
Jonathan Latko Computer Recycling Center, Temple University
Jessa Lingel Associate Professor, Annenberg School for Communication, University of Pennsylvania</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Our team includes six staff and over 50 volunteers from a wide array of local and national organizations. For more information, visit our people page.
The Big Picture Alliance recently completed a documentary film about the early stages of the PCW project. Check it out on YouTube.
For up to date info on the project, sign up for our newsletter!
Vision Just before the COVID-19 pandemic hit, a detailed study published by the Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia found that a mere 53% of Black residents and 44% of Latinx residents in Philadelphia have broadband connections (Alvaro 2020).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Wermer-Colan</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/alexwc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/alexwc/</guid>
      <description>Alex Wermer-Colan is the Executive Director of Philly Community Wireless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allan Gomez</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/allang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/allang/</guid>
      <description>Allan Gomez is the Systems Adminstrator for Philly Community Wireless. With PCW, he helps manage and expand a growing community WiFi network in Philadelphia. He also helps to build engagement and ownership with community members. The work that he does with PCW overlaps nicely with his past experiences of building low-power FM radio stations throughout Latin America and the United States. In addition, he makes a Sisyphean effort at raising his two daughters cross-culturally with a strong commitment to justice and solidarity, and a love of music, art, and science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Mehretab</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/chrism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/chrism/</guid>
      <description>Originally from Harrisburg, PA, Chris initially joined the PCW team as an Intern in the Summer of 2021. From there, his work grew as the Community Engagement Liaison, into his current role as Social Media Manager. He has assisted in multiple outreach forums including canvassing, tabling for community events, and operating all PCW related social media channels. Outside of PCW, Chris works at a law firm in the city and enjoys DJing and playing with his cat Puffin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Hutchinson</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/dylanh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/dylanh/</guid>
      <description>Dylan grew up in the Lehigh Valley region of Pennsylvania, just north of Philadelphia. Dylan graduated from Moravian University in the Spring of 2021 with a bachelors of science degree in Public Health and Computer Science.
Shortly after graduation, Dylan moved to the Philadelphia suburbs where he took a job working as an observability and monitoring engineer at a large financial institution. Dylan in the past worked as an emergency medical technician and dispatcher where he discovered his love for community and working with people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eugene Ryoo</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/eugener/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/eugener/</guid>
      <description>Eugene is an Install Lead with Philly Community Wireless. He grew up in central Pennsylvania and moved to Philadelphia in the summer of 2022 to work as a cybersecurity consultant for a professional services firm. Primarily interested in the relationship between people and technology, Eugene does a bit of everything with PCW, from helping out with installs to writing and maintaining web applications. Outside of work, Eugene enjoys going to shows, playing guitar and bass, cycling, and hanging out at home with his cat, Toes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leanne Przybylowski</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/leannep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/leannep/</guid>
      <description>A Canadian, Leanne came to Philadelphia in 2021 to pursue a Master’s of Science in Communication for Development and Social Change at Temple University. Interested in digital equity and the link between digital spaces and healthy democracy, Leanne began volunteering with PCW at the end of her time at Temple, and quickly became quite active in the organization and passionate about its alternative vision for transforming digital inclusion through community wifi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mir Detre</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/mird/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/mird/</guid>
      <description>Mir is the full-time technician at Philly Community Wireless. Their primary work with PCW is doing on-site installation and maintenance work. Their educational background is in Systems Engineering, while their professional background spans from fabrication to batista work to costume design. They enjoy the hands-on, troubleshooting work of building a community-controlled wireless network. The work of directly providing internet accessibility, one radio and one AP at a time, aligns perfectly with Mir&amp;rsquo;s values and philosophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/airmonitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/airmonitor/</guid>
      <description>Act on Air: The Philly Air Monitor Project Philly Community Wireless is partnering with other organizations around the city, including the Clean Air Council and Temple University&amp;rsquo;s Geography and Urban Studies Program, to deploy Purple Air Monitors on our network.
Measuring Air Quality Purple Air monitors allow residents to asses:
If their air quality is good in their area How it compares to other parts of the city. Purple Air Monitors Purple air monitors enable communities to engage in citizen science around pollution in their neighborhoods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Coverage Map</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/networkmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/networkmap/</guid>
      <description>Philly Community Wireless Wifi Coverage Map To view the map in fullscreen, visit this webpage.
This map focuses on showing the overall network architecture. Points on the map represent outdoor wifi access points primarily. Any area covered by the heatmap should have PCW signal available for a free wifi connection.
Please keep in mind that the heatmap is not accurate at the street-level, and if you cannot access the wifi network in any given space in the city, you may need to walk around a street corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/faq/</guid>
      <description>Who are we? What is Philly Community Wireless? Philly Community Wireless is a community organization developing community-owned mesh networks in North Philly. We are a working group of organizers, technologists, academics, public school teachers, and City Hall staffers in Philadelphia. We seek to address the city&amp;rsquo;s digital divide with community-owned and -operated mesh network technologies.
Mesh networks allow a single Internet connection to be shared among a broader group of users with very little cost or infrastructure required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get connected</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/getconnected/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/getconnected/</guid>
      <description>Sign Up! If you live in the North Philadelphia neighborhoods of Fairhill, Kensington, and Norris Square, and want to get connected to free wireless internet, or host an antenna to connect your neighbors, please fill out our Sign Up Form!
The Installation Process Philly Community Wireless works with PhillyWisper, a local wireless internet service provider, to install rooftop antennas that we use to provide a free wifi network to the neighborhood residents and public spaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/termsofservice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/termsofservice/</guid>
      <description>Philly Community Wireless is a free, public wifi network. To use this free wifi network, you agree to our following Terms of Service.
Terms of Service The Philly Community Wireless Project, a fiscally sponsored project of the Movement Alliance Project (“PCWP”) and its backhaul provider, PhillyWisper (“PW”), support net neutrality and a free and open Internet without throttling, zero-rating, or tracking people’s usage for money, advertising, or other forms of consideration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCW Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Values of Participation This is a safe space. We encourage discussion of sensitive and difficult topics so that we can support each other and problem solve together. At the same time, we strive to uphold spaces where people with a plurality of voices and experiences can participate in full. Due to the sensitive or private nature of some elements of the project, please be cognizant to avoid sharing identifying information, and remember that anything you do share is seen by other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Notice</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Effective Date: March 1, 2021
Last Updated: May 21, 2021
We at Philadelphia Community Wireless Project, a fiscally sponsored project of the Movement Alliance Project (&amp;quot;PCWP&amp;quot;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;) are strongly committed to transparency, and we want you (&amp;quot;you&amp;quot; or &amp;ldquo;your&amp;rdquo;) to understand how we collect, use, share and protect your personal information, as well as how you can manage the personal information we collect. This Privacy Notice applies to your interactions with us, including attending our events or participating in our programs, or your use of our website (www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/resources/</guid>
      <description>Last Updated: January 6, 2024
Below are some more materials and resources to help you find digital resources for wifi access, computer use, and more. Check them out!
Digital Literacy Training and Technical Support - Digital Equity Center at Temple University Description: Provides an on-site open computer lab, digital literacy training, affordable internet options, home computer solutions, and technical support via their hotline.
Location: 1918 N 11th St, Philadelphia PA 19122.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>We love volunteers! We&amp;rsquo;re a volunteer-led coalition working to build community controlled wireless internet networks in Philadelphia. Below we&amp;rsquo;ve outlined ways that volunteers can contribute.
If you’re interested in getting involved, please fill out our Volunteer Sign-Up Form.
Tech Volunteers The Tech Team is actively seeking volunteers to help with our installation process: attending in-person trainings in Norris Square, configuring our networking hardware, and installing equipment in homes and on rooftops throughout Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
