<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acerca de Nosotros on Philly Community Wireless</title>
    <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acerca de Nosotros on Philly Community Wireless</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Socios</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/partners/</guid>
      <description>Socios comunitarios de Norris Square Friends of Norris Square Park GALAEI Kensington Branch of the Free Library Xiente (anteriormente Norris Square Community Alliance) Norris Square Neighborhood Project Open Kitchen Sculpture Garden West Kensington Ministries Cesar Andreu Iglesias Gardens Socios de la comunidad de Philadelphia PhillyWisper Called to Serve Free Library of Philadelphia HACE Holobiont Lab Village of the Arts and Humanities Philly Tech Justice Temple University, Digital Equity Center Kensington Corridor Trust Fundadores Para más información sobre nuestros financiadores institucionales, visite nuestra página Fundadores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundadores</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/funders/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/funders/</guid>
      <description> Better Bike Share Partnership Mini Grant, Philadelphia City Fund, 2024 Community Challenge Grant, AARP (American Association of Retired Persons), 2023 Digital Equity Grant y apoyo continuo del Independent Public Media Foundation, 2021 hasta el presente Digital Literacy Alliance, The Mayor&#39;s Fund for Philadelphia, 2021-2022 Rapid Response Magic Project of the Princeton Humanities Council, 2020 RISE (Recognizing Inequalities and Standing for Equality), Pace Center for Civic Engagement, 2020 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preguntas más frecuentes</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/faq/</guid>
      <description>¿Quien Somos Nosotros? ¿Qué es Philly Community Wireless? Philly Community Wireless es una organización comunitaria que desarrolla redes de malla de propiedad comunitaria en el norte de Filadelfia. Somos un grupo de trabajo de organizadores, tecnólogos, académicos, maestros de escuelas públicas y personal del Ayuntamiento de Filadelfia. Buscamos abordar la brecha digital de la ciudad con tecnologías de red de malla operadas y propiedad de la comunidad.
Las redes de malla permiten compartir una única conexión a Internet entre un grupo más amplio de usuarios con muy poco coste o infraestructura necesaria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cómo llegar aquí</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/location/</guid>
      <description>PCW is located at the Norris Square Neighborhood Project at 2141 N Howard Street, adjacent to Norris Square Park.
Public Transit NSNP is a quick walk from either the York-Dauphin or Berks Market-Frankford Line SEPTA stops.
Driving Street parking is available around Norris Square Park; availabiliy is limited.
Cycling There is an Indego stop a ~5 minute walk away at 2nd and Norris next to The Ground Coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Novedades</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/es/about/news/</guid>
      <description>Tech Policy, America, Disconnected: What’s Biden’s Plan for Averting Digital Disaster?, 4/30/2024
CNET, Alternative Broadband Networks: Affordable Internet for the People, One Rooftop at a Time, 10/1/2023
Kensington Voice, Norris Square organization increases community access to free internet, 7/12/2023
Technical.ly Philly, Alex Wermer-Colan and PCW awarded Community Tech Leader of the Year 2022, 12/14/2022
Al Dia, Bringing Digital Equity to North Philadelphia, 5/13/2022
Technical.ly Philly, A group of Philly technologists are working on a free, community-based mesh Wi-Fi network, 2/1/2022</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
