<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Session Notes on Philly Community Wireless Project</title>
    <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.com/sessions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Session Notes on Philly Community Wireless Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://phillycommunitywireless.com/sessions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Session 13</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.com/sessions/2020-07-15-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.com/sessions/2020-07-15-session/</guid>
      <description>In this meeting, we 1) heard from Reverend Mike Major about his North Philadelphia Collective, 2) discussed potential install sites, and 3) creating jobs through the project. Also, many of us will be attending the 21st Allied Media Conference.
  Reverend Mike Major shared his [white paper][1] where he outlined solutions to the problem of providing fast and free Internet access to 2,000 students. Reverend Mike&amp;rsquo;s background is software development; he also donates his time to revitalizing North Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 12</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.com/sessions/2020-07-8-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.com/sessions/2020-07-8-session/</guid>
      <description>In this meetings, we 1) reviewed website updates 2) further defined the project&amp;rsquo;s scope, and 3) discussed measurement metrics for broadband.
  We discussed what we can put on the website to involve the community, invite more people join our mailing list and weekly meetings. New volunteers need to be able to get up to speed with our progress, as well as the public and community needs to understand how decisions are being made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 2</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.com/sessions/may-13-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.com/sessions/may-13-2020/</guid>
      <description>In this meeting, we heard from 1) Meta Mesh in Pittsburg, 2) Community Tech NY, 3) Andrew Coy in Baltimore, and 4) we discussed some Philly specific planning.
  Adam Longwill, part of Meta Mesh, tells the group about PittMesh, a community wireless network in Pittsburgh under the auspices of non-profit Meta Mesh Wireless Communities. Adam advises that the network installation and maintenance should be left to the non-profit due to the intense work of building the network and the high expenditure of resources needed to educate a community on network maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 1</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.com/sessions/may-6-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.com/sessions/may-6-2020/</guid>
      <description>In our first official meeting, we overview 1) how mesh networks work, 2) Raul Enrequez from Community Tech NY and David Johnson with iNethi speak on their community network projects, and 3) Fraca Muller of the Baltimore Teachers Union and Andrew Coy of the Digital Harbor Foundation speak on their digital inclusion efforts in Baltimore, and 4) we begin conversations about Philly Wisper in Philadelphia.
  In Community Tech NY, multiple communities around the city decide where a network goes and builds it jointly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
