<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>People on Philly Community Wireless</title>
    <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in People on Philly Community Wireless</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Zoe Kerrich</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/zoek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/zoek/</guid>
      <description>Zoe began volunteering with Philly Community Wireless in the summer of 2024, and currently supports wifi access installation work. She has a background in city and regional planning, with a focus in climate resilience planning. Outside of work, Zoe enjoys gardening, biking, and weaving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Wermer-Colan</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/alexwc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/alexwc/</guid>
      <description>Alex Wermer-Colan is a co-founder, long-time volunteer, and Executive Director of Philly Community Wireless. A resident of North Philadelphia, Alex also works as the Academic and Research Director at Temple University Libraries&amp;rsquo; Loretta C. Duckworth Scholars Studio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allan Gomez</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/allang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/allang/</guid>
      <description>Allan Gomez is the Systems Adminstrator for Philly Community Wireless. With PCW, he helps manage and expand a growing community wifi network in Philadelphia. He also helps to build engagement and ownership with community members. The work that he does with PCW overlaps nicely with his past experiences of building low-power FM radio stations throughout Latin America and the United States. In addition, he makes a Sisyphean effort at raising his two daughters cross-culturally with a strong commitment to justice and solidarity, and a love of music, art, and science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Mehretab</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/chrism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/chrism/</guid>
      <description>Originally from Harrisburg, PA, Chris initially joined the PCW team as an Intern in the Summer of 2021. From there, his work grew as the Community Engagement Liaison, into his current role as Content Coordinator. He has assisted in multiple outreach forums including canvassing, tabling for community events, and operating all PCW related social media channels. Outside of PCW, Chris works at a law firm in the city and enjoys DJing and playing with his cat Puffin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Hutchinson</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/dylanh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/dylanh/</guid>
      <description>Dylan grew up in the Lehigh Valley region of Pennsylvania, just north of Philadelphia. Dylan graduated from Moravian University in the Spring of 2021 with a bachelors of science degree in Public Health and Computer Science.
Shortly after graduation, Dylan moved to the Philadelphia suburbs where he took a job working as an observability and monitoring engineer at a large financial institution. Dylan in the past worked as an emergency medical technician and dispatcher where he discovered his love for community and working with people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eugene Ryoo</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/eugener/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/eugener/</guid>
      <description>Eugene is the Technician with Philly Community Wireless. He grew up in central Pennsylvania and moved to Philadelphia in the summer of 2022. Primarily interested in the relationship between people and technology, Eugene&amp;rsquo;s role include leading installations, writing and maintaining web applications, and creating documentation. Outside of work, Eugene enjoys going to shows, playing guitar and bass, cycling, and hanging out at home with his cat, Toes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leanne Przybylowski</title>
      <link>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/leannep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phillycommunitywireless.org/about/people/leannep/</guid>
      <description>A Canadian, Leanne came to Philadelphia in 2021 to pursue a Master’s of Science in Communication for Development and Social Change at Temple University. Interested in digital equity and the link between digital spaces and healthy democracy, Leanne began volunteering with PCW in Summer 2023, quickly becoming quite active in the organization and passionate about its alternative vision for transforming digital inclusion through community wifi. She is excited to learn and grow alongside community members, local leaders, and her colleagues.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
